<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd">
<identifier type="local">IMT-T67</identifier>
<titleinfo><title>Indians for Indians Radio Show, Undated</title></titleinfo>
<typeOfResource>Sound Recording</typeOfResource>
<name><namePart>Don Whistler</namePart><role><roleTerm type="text">host or master of ceremonies</roleTerm></role></name>
<note type="broadcast number">181</note>
<note type="broadcast note">Don Whistler, Announcer for "Indians for Indians."  Program is one hour long.</note>
<tableOfContents>
"Indians for Indians" Program put on by Summer Institute of Linguistics personnel brought by Mose Poolaw, Kiowa.  Program consists of numbers by white students attending linguistics institute and Indian informants, and one drum rhythm number by a Liberian man attending the institute.  
1. Arapaho hymn sung by student (Flora Clark).  
2. Reading of verse from Bible in Shawnee by Sue Albright, white student of Lucinda Haury.  
3. Comanche hymn sung by group led by Joe Haury.  
4. Comanche hymn sung by group led by Cynthia Webb.  
5. Cherokee composition by Al Pinz (student) and Martin Johnson (informant) - conversation in Cherokee.  
6. Cheyenne hymn sung by Cheyenne women informants.  
7. Liberian drum rhythms played by Gus Mars, student from Liberia.  
8. Reading of verse from Bible in Comanche by Ivan Low, student of Clifford Seymour.  
9. Comanche hymn sung by students of informant Clifford Seymour.  
10. Kiowa conversation between white student and Kiowa informant, William Wolf.  
11. Kiowa hymn sung by Dan Stookey in Kiowa.  This is the "Prayer Song."  
12. Reading of scripture verse in English and Kiowa by Dean Stookey.  
13. Reading of scripture verse in English and Kiowa by another student.  
14. Arapaho testimony by Louise Bass, student of Lizzie Left Hand.  
15. Arapaho hymn sung by students of Lizzie Left Hand.  
16. Cheyenne translation of a Bible verse by student of Miss Big Horse.
</tableOfContents>
<note type="tape number">67</note>
<originInfo><dateCreated>Undated</dateCreated></originInfo>
<subject><topical>Mixture</topical></subject><note type="preferred citation">When citing recordings from this collection, please using the following:  Indians for Indians Radio Show. Western History Collections, University of Oklahoma Libraries.</note><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="https://rightsstatements.org/vocab/InC-NC/1.0/"/>
</mods>
